Guide to the Office of the Secretary, Yale University, Annual Reports Submitted to the President
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Office of the Secretary, Yale University, annual reports submitted to the president
1985-2001
RU 219
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
27.92
(48 boxes)
The records consist of annual reports from academic departments and programs, residential colleges, graduate and professional schools, and administrative offices of Yale University.
Yale University. Office of the Secretary
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 4-A (YRG 4-A), Records of the Yale secretary's office.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged chronologically by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of annual reports from academic departments and programs, residential colleges, graduate and professional schools, and administrative offices of Yale University.
Universities and colleges -- Administration; Universities and colleges -- Departments; Annual reports; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Departments; Yale University. Office of the Secretary; Yale University. President's Office
- Annual reports submitted to the president, 1985-1989; Accession 1992-A-020
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2024
  - American Studies Program, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Anesthesiology, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Anthropology, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Applied Physics, Section of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Architecture, School of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 5 - 6)
  - Association of Yale Alumni, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Astronomy, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation, Department of, 1986-87 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Berkeley College, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Biology, Department of, 1987-1988, 1988-89 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Branford College, 1987-1988, 1988-89 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - British Art, Yale Center for, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Calhoun College, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Career Services, University, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Cell Biology, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Cellular and Molecular Physiology, Department of (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Chemical Engineering, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Chemistry, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Child Study Center, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Classics, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Comparative Literature, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Comparative Medicine, Section of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Computer Science, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Davenport College, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Dermatology, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Diagnostic Radiology, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Divinity School, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Drama, School of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Timothy Dwight College, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - East Asian Languages and Literatures, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - East Asian Studies, Council on, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Economic Growth Center, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Economics, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Jonathan Edwards College, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Electrical Engineering, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Engineering, Council on, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - English, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Films, Yale University, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, School of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - French, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Geology and Geophysics, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Germanic Languages and Literatures, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Graduate School, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Health Services, Yale University, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - History, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - History of Art, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - History of Medicine, Section of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - History of Science, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Human Genetics, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Internal Medicine, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - International and Area Studies, Yale Center for, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Italian Language and Literature, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Judaic Studies, Undergraduate Program in, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Laboratory Medicine, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Language Laboratory, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Law School, Yale, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Linguistics, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Mathematics, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Mechanical Engineering, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Medicine, School of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Medieval Studies, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Molecular Neurobiology, Section of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Morse College, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Music, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Music, Yale School of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Near Eastern Languages and Civilizations, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Neuroanatomy, Section of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Neurology, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Nursing, School of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Obstetrics and Gynecology, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Opthalmology and Visual Science, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Organization and Management, School of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Orthopaedics and Rehabilitation, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Pathology, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 78 - 80)
  - Paediatrics, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Pharmacology, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Philosophy, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Physics, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Pierson College, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Police Department, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Political Science, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Poynter Fellowship in Journalism, 1987-1988, 1988-89 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Psychiatry, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Public Health, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Public Information, Office of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Regional Council on Education for Employment, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Religious Ministry, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Religious Studies, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Renaissance Studies, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Sacred Music, Yale Institute of, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Saybrook College, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Slavic Languages and Literatures, Department of, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Sociology, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Spanish and Portuguese, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Special Students, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Statistics, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Ezra Stiles College, 1986-87 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Surgery, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Teacher Preparation Program, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Therapeutic Radiology, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Trumbull College, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Yale University Art Gallery, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Women's Studies Program, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Yale-China Association, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Yale College, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Yale College Council, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 112)
- Annual reports submitted to the president, 1988-1990; Accession 1993-A-011
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2026
  - 1988-1989
    - AMERICAN STUDIES, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ANESTHESIOLOGY, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - ANCHROPOLOGY, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - APPLIED PHYSICS, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - ARCHITECTURE, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - ASTRONOMY, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - ATHLETICS, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - BERKELEY COUGE, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - BIOLOGY, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - BRANFORD COLLEGE, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - BRITISH ART CENTER; COMBINED WITH 1989-1 990 REPORT, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - BUSH CENTER IN CHILD DEVELOPMENT AND SOCIAL POLICY, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - CALHOUN CUUEGE, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - CELL BIOLOGY, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - CELLULAR AND MOLECULAR PHYSIOLOGY, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - CHEMICAL ENGINEERING, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - CHEMISTRY, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - CHID STUDY CENTER, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - CLASSICS, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - COMPARATIVE LITERATURE, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - COMPARATIVE MEDICINE, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - COMPUTER SCIENCE, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - DAVENPORT COLLEGE, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - DEMTOLOGY, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - DIAGNOSTIC RADIOLOGY, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - DIVINITY SCHOOL, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - DRAMA, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - DWIGHT, TIMOTHY, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - EAST ASIAN LANGUAGES AND LITERATURES, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - EAST ASIAN STUDIES, COUNCIL ON, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - ECONOMICS, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - ECONOMIC GROWTH CEMER, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - ENGINEERING, COUNCIL ON, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - ENGLISH, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - EPIDEMIOLOGY AND PUBLIC HEALTH, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - FILM STUDIES PROGRAM, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - FORESTRY AND ENVIRONMENTAL STUDIES, SCHOOL OF, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - FRENCH, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - GEOLOGY AND GEOPHYSICS, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - GERMANIC LANGUAGES AND LITERATURES, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - GRADUATE SCHOOL, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - HEALTH SERVICES, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - HISTORY, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - HISTORY OF ART, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - HISTORY OF MEDICINE, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - HISTORY OF SCIENCE, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - HUMAN GENETICS, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - INTERNAL MEDICINE, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - INTERNATIONAL AND AREA STUDIES, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - ITALIAN LANGUAGE AND LITERATURE, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - JUDAIC STUDIES, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - LABORATORY MEDICINE, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - LANGUAGE LABORATORY, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - LINGUISTICS, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - MATHEMATICS, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - MEDICINE, SCHOOL OF, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - MECHANICAL ENGINEERING, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - MEDIEVAL STUDIES, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - MOLECULAR BIOPHYSICS AND BIOCHEMISTRY, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - MOLECULAR NEUROBIOLOGY, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - MORSE COUEGE, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - MUSIC, SCHOOL OF, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - NEAR EASTERN LANGUAGES AND CIVILIZATIONS, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - NEUROANATOMY, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - NEUROLOGY, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - NURSING, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - OBSTETRICS and GYNECOLOGY, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - OPKTHALMOLOGY AND VISUAL SCIENCE, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - ORGANIZATION AND MANAGEMENT, SCHOOL OF, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - ORTHOPAEDICS and REHABILITATION, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - PATHOLOGY, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - PEDIATRICS, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - PHARMACOLOGY, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - PHILOSOPW, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - PHYSICS, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - POLICE, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - POLITICAL SCIENCE, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - PSYCHIATRIC INSTITUTE, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - PSYCHIATRY, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - PUBLIC INFORMATION, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - RELIGIOUS STUDIES, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - RENAISSANCE STUDIES, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - SACRED MUSIC; INSTITUTE OF, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - SAYBROOK COLLEGE, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - SLAVIC LANGUAGES AND LITERATURES, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - SOCIAL AND POLICY STUDIES, INSTITUTE OF, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - SOCIOLOGY, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - SPANISH and PORTUGUESE, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - STATISTICS, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - SUMMER AND SPECIAL PROGRAMS, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - SURGERY, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - EZRA STILES, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - TEACHERS INSTITUTE, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - TEACHER PREPARATION, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - THEREPEUTIC RADIOLOGY, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - TRUMBUU COUEGE, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - UNIVERSITY CAREER SERVICES, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - WOMEN'S STUDIES PROGRAM, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - YALE COUEGE, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - YALE-NEW HAVEN HOSPITAL, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - 1989-1990
    - ALUMNI FUND, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - AMERICAN STUDIES, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - ANESTHESIOLOGY, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 104)
    - AMHROPOtOGY, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 105)
    - APPLIED PHYSICS, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - ARCHITKTURE, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 107)
    - ASTRONOMY, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 108)
    - ATHLETICS, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 109)
    - BERKELEY COUEGE, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - BIOLOGY, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 111)
    - BRANFORD COLLEGE; COMBINED WITH 1988-1989 REPORT, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 112)
    - BRITISH ART CENTER, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 113)
    - CAREER SERVICES, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 114)
    - CELL BIOLOGY, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 115)
    - CEUULAR MOLECULAR PHYSIOLOGY, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 116)
    - CHAPLAIN'S OFFICE, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 117)
    - CHEMICAL ENGINEERING, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 118)
    - CHEMISTRY, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 119)
    - CHILD STUDY CENTER, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 120)
    - CUI\SSICS, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 121)
    - COMPARATIVE LITERATURE, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 122)
    - COMPARATIVE MEDICINE, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 123)
    - COMPUTER SCIENCE, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 124)
    - DAVENPORT COLLEGE, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 125)
    - DERMATOLOGY, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 126)
    - DIAGNOSTIC RADIOLOGY, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 127)
    - DIVINITY SCHOOL, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 128)
    - DRAMA, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 129)
    - DWIGHT, TIMOTHY, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 130)
    - EAST ASIAN LANGUAGES AND LITERATURES, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 131)
    - EAST ASIAN STUDIES, COUNCIL ON, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 132)
    - ECONOMIC GROWTH CEMER, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 133)
    - ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING, COUNCIL ON, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 134)
    - ENGINEERING, COUNCIL ON, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 135)
    - ENGLISH, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 136)
    - EPIDEMIOLOGY AND PUBLIC HEALTH, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 137)
    - FORESTRY AND ENVIRONMENTAL STUDIES, SCHOOL OF, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 138)
    - GEOLOGY AND GEOPHYSICS, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 139)
    - GERMANIC LANGUAGES AND LITERATURES, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 140)
    - GRADUATE SCHOOL, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 141)
    - HEALTH SERVICES, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 142)
    - HISTORY, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 143)
    - HISTORY OF ART, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 144)
    - HISTORY-OF MEDICINE, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 145)
    - HISTORY OF SCIENCE, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 146)
    - HUMAN GENETICS, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 147)
    - INTERNAL MEDICINE, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 148)
    - INTERNATIONAL AND AREA STUDIES, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 149)
    - ITALIAN LANGUAGE AND LITERATURES, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 150)
    - JUDAIC STUDIES, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 151)
    - LABORATORY MEDICINE, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 152)
    - LANGUAGE LABORATORY, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 153)
    - ORVILLE H. SCHELL, JR. CENTER FOR INTERNATIONAL HUMAN RIGHTS LAW, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 154)
    - LINGUISTICS, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 155)
    - MATHEMATICS, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 156)
    - MECHANICAL ENGINEERING, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 157)
    - MEDICINE, SCHOOL OF, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 158)
    - MOLECULAR BIOPHYSICS AND BIOCHEMISTRY, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 159)
    - MOLECUUR MEDICINE, CENTER FOR, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 160)
    - MORSE COLLEGE, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 161)
    - MUSIC, DEPARTMENT OF, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 162)
    - MUSIC, SCHOOL OF, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 163)
    - NEAR EASTERN LANGUAGES AND CIVILIZATIONS, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 164)
    - NEUROANATOMY, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 165)
    - NEUROLOGY, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 166)
    - NURSING, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 167)
    - OPHTHALMOLOGY AND VISUAL SCIENCE, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 168)
    - ORGANIZATION AND MANAGEMENT, SCHOOL OF, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 169)
    - ORTHOPAEDICS AND REHABILITATION, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 170)
    - PATHOLOGY, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 171)
    - PEABODY MUSEUM, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 172)
    - PEDIATRICS, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 173)
    - PHARMACOLOGY, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 174)
    - PHILOSOPHY, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 175)
    - PHYSICS, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 176)
    - POLITICAL SCIENCE, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 177)
    - POLICE DEPARTMENT, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 178)
    - PSYCHIATRY, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 179)
    - PSYCHIATRIC INSTITUTE, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 180)
    - RELIGIOUS STUDIES, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 181)
    - RENAISSANCE STUDlES, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 182)
    - SAYBROOK W G E, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 183)
    - SLAVIC LANGUAGES AND LITERATURES, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 184)
    - SOCIAL AND POLICY STUDIES, INSTITUTE FOR, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 185)
    - SOClOLOGY, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 186)
    - SPANISH AND PORTUGUESE, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 187)
    - STATISTICS, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 188)
    - SURGERY, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 189)
    - TEACHER INSTITUTE, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 190)
    - TEACHER PREPARATION, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 191)
    - THERAPEUTIC RADIOLOGY, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 192)
    - TRUMBUU COLLEGE, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 193)
    - WOMEN'S STUDIES, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 194)
- Annual reports submitted to the president, 1990-1991; Accession 1994-A-008
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2027
  - American Studies, 1991 August (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Anesthesiology, 1991 November (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Anthropotogy, Michael D. Coe, 1991 October (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Applied Physics, Werner P. Wolf, 1991 August (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Architecture, School of, Dean Thomas H.Beeby, 1992 January (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Art, School of, David Pease, 1991 January (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Astronomy, Augustus Oemler, 1992 December (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Athtetics, H.E. Woodsum, Jr., 1992 May (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Biology, 1991 August (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Calhoun College, E. Onat, 1991 September (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Career Services, 1991 October (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Cell Biology, James D. Jamieson, 1991 October (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Cellular and Molecular Physiology, Robert I.White, Jr., M.D., 1991 September (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Chaplaincy, University, Harry B. Adams, 1991 June (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Chemical Engineering, 1992 May (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Chemistry, Frederick E. Ziegler, 1991 August (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Child Study Center, Donald J. Cohen, M.D., 1991 October (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Classics, Gordon W. Williams, 1992 April (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Comparative Literature, David Marshall, 1991 September (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Comparative Medicine, Section of, Robert 0. Joacoby, Ph.D., 1991 September (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Computer Science, 1991 November (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Davenport College, Henry Turner, 1991 July (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Dermatology, Richard L. Edelson, M.D., 1991 August (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Diagnostic Radiology Robert I White, Jr., 1992 April (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Drama Repertory Theatre, Earle R Gister, 1991 June (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - East Asian Languages and Literatures, Edwin McClellan, 1991 December (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - East Asian Studies, Council on, William W. Kelly, 1991 October (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Economic Growth Center, T. Paul Schultz, 1991 August (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Electrical Engineering, Peter M. Schultheiss, 1991 November (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - English Department, Richard H. Brodhead, 1991 August (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health, 1992 June (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Ezra Stiles, T. Lawler, 1992 April (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, School of, John C. Gordon, 1991 October (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - French, Ora Avni, 1992 May (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Genetics, 1991 November (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Geology and Geophysics, Barry Saltrnan, 1991 July (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Germanic Languages and Literatures, Jeffrley L. Sammons, 1991 June (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Graduate School, 1992 March
  - Health Services, Dr. Stephanie Spangler, 1992 January (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - History, John Boswell, 1991 November (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - History of Art, Jules D. Prown, 1991 August (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - History of Medicine, Frederick L. Holmes, 1992 April (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - History of Science, Asger Aaboe, 1992 May (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Immunobiology, Section of, Richard Flavell, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Internal Medicine, Ed Cadman, M.D., 1991 April (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - International and Area Studies, Center for, 1992 June (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Itatian Language and Literature, Giuseppe Mazzotta, 1991 September (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Jonathan Edwards College, Bernard Lytton, 1991 August (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Judaic Studies Program, Paula E.Hyman, 1991 July (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Laboratory Medicine, Dr. peter Jatlow, 1992 January (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Language Laboratory, Pierre J.Capretz, 1992 April (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Linguistics, Laurence R. Horn (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Mechanical Engineering (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Medicine, School of Robert H. Donaldson, Jr., M.D., 1991 December (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Medieval Studies, Trinnual Report of, Ingeborg Glier, 1992 May (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry, Donald M. Engelman, 1991 July (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Molecular Medicine, Boyer Center for, Vincent T. Marchesi, M.D., 1991 October (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Morse College, Donald Quinlan, 1991 August (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Music, Dept. of, Craig Wright, 1992 February (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Music, School of, 1991 September (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Near Eastern Languages and Civitizations, Benjamin R. Foster, 1992 February (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Neurobiology, Section of, Pasko Rakic, H.O., 1991 October (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Neurology, Stephen G. Waxman, 1991 August (Box 4, Folder 62)